Menu

Bespoke Privacy Policy
======================

### Effective Date: December 5, 2022

Your privacy is important to us. Therefore, the Company has adopted this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) in order to provide you (“you” or “User”) with information regarding the Company’s collection and use of your personal and personally identifiable information. By using the services offered by the Company (the “Services”), you consent to the Privacy Policy. The Company reserves the right to suspend, replace, modify, amend, or terminate this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, and within its sole and absolute discretion. In the event the Company replaces, modifies, or amends this Privacy Policy, the Effective Date above will change. Your continued use of the Services after a change in the Effective Date constitutes your agreement to said replacement, modification, or amendment. It is your obligation to periodically check this Privacy Policy for changes.

### Information Company Collects

In order to utilize the Services, the Company may collect personal and personally identifiable information from you. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, date of birth and a username and password for an account that is unique to you. Additionally, the Company may capture other information including, but not limited to, your IP address, geolocation, information stored in cookies, pixel tags, and web beacons.

### Cookies

The Company’s website may use cookies. Cookies are small data files generally comprised of a string of text and numbers that assign your computer a unique identifier. They collect information from your computer and allow your computer to have a “dialogue” with the Company and gives you a more convenient and personalized experience with the Company’s website. If you do not want the Company to use cookies with your computer, then you must adjust your browser settings in order to disable them. Please note, however, that the disabling of cookies may prevent you from fully accessing all features of the Company’s website. If you require any assistance in disabling cookies, please contact your browser company.

### Social Networking Data

In the event that the Company allows you to integrate any social media function—eg. use of Facebook, Twitter, or LinkedIn—into your use of the Company’s website, the Company may collect your username associated with any such social media website you use. We may also collect any information that you make public through that website or that such website has shared with us, including, but not limited to profile information, pages you have “liked,” and friend lists.

### Disclosure and Use of Information

By using the Services you acknowledge and agree that the Company may release your personal or personally identifiable information to third-party contractors or their agents that have formed a relationship with the Company or may use it to promote its services and offerings via email, phone or SMS/text messaging. Company may also transfer your personal or personally identifiable information to respond to a duly authorized subpoena or court order, to respond to regulatory requests by government authorities, to protect the safety or security of the Company, the Services, its employees, and its users, and, where necessary, to protect against fraud, false advertising, or the violation of any law, statute, ordinance, regulation, or treaty, whether local, state, provincial, national or international.

### Security of Information

The Company works to protect the security of your personal and personally identifiable information using commercially reasonable security measures and has implemented industry standard encryption to protect against unauthorized access to or interception of your personal and personally identifiable information. However, no security measures entirely impenetrable. As such, the Company is not responsible for the circumvention of its security measures by any User or third parties.

### Join Our Discord Community

About
-----

Getting Started
---------------

Resources
---------

About
-----

Social Media
------------

Follow us on social media to find out the latest updates on our progress

Don’t miss our future updates! Get Subscribed Today!

Submit

All the information on this website – www.bespokefundingprogram.com – is published in good faith and for general information purpose only. Bespoke Funding does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on this website (Bespoke Educational Services – FZCO –  
Dubai Silicon Oasis, DDP, Building A1, Dubai, United Arab Emirates), is strictly at your own risk. Bespoke Educational Services – FZCO not be liable for any losses and/or damages in connection with the use of our website. From our website, you can visit other websites by following hyperlinks to such external sites. While we strive to provide only quality links to useful and ethical websites, we have no control over the content and nature of these sites. These links to other websites do not imply a recommendation for all the content found on these sites. Site owners and content may change without notice and may occur before we have the opportunity to remove a link which may have gone ‘bad’. Please be also aware that when you leave our website, other sites may have different privacy policies and terms which are beyond our control. Please be sure to check the Privacy Policies of these sites as well as their “Terms of Service” before engaging in any business or uploading any information. This website is the property of \[Bespoke Educational Services – FZCO\] and shall not be reproduced, copied in whole or in part, adapted, modified, disseminated or scraped without the express prior written consent of \[Bespoke Educational Services – FZCO\]

Copyright © 2024 [bespokefundingprogram.com](https://www.bespokefundingprogram.com/ "Bespokefundingprogram.com") All Rights Reserved.  
Development by [Hammani Tech](https://hammanitech.com/ "Bespokefundingprogram.com")

Challenge Type
--------------

* Traders Choice
* Standard Challenge

Account Size
------------

* $10,000
* $25,000
* $50,000
* $100,000
* $200,000
* $300,000
* $400,000

Account Type
------------

* Regular
* Swap Free <span class="twoswap" >+20% Fee </span>

Trading Platform
----------------

* MT4
* MT5
